{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Will she come tonight? I ______.",
      "a": "don't think so",
      "b": "think not",
      "c": "don't think",
      "d": "think so nol",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Hope/ think/ afraid/ say +so: used to refer back to an idea, action, quality, situation etc that has just been mentioned ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is he coming? 'I ______'",
      "a": "believe yes",
      "b": "believe so",
      "c": "don't believe so",
      "d": "don't believe",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Hope/ think/ afraid/ say + so: used to refer back to an idea, action, quality, situation etc that has just been mentioned ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Susan, _____ so many things!",
      "a": "don't buy",
      "b": "buy",
      "c": "buy not",
      "d": "buy no",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is she coming? '______'",
      "a": "I don't hope so",
      "b": "I hope that nol",
      "c": "I hope not",
      "d": "I don't hope",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- I hope not: used to say that you hope something that has been mentioned does not happen or is not true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mr. Brown,______ with me, please.",
      "a": "come",
      "b": "come you",
      "c": "you come",
      "d": "comes",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will your sister come for Christmas?''I _____ '",
      "a": "hope that yes",
      "b": "hope yes",
      "c": "think that yes",
      "d": "hope so",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- I hope so:spoken used to say that you hope something that has been mentioned happens or is true ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Children, ______ your homework, tonight!",
      "a": "make",
      "b": "do",
      "c": "you do",
      "d": "do you",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Carol, ______all the milk!",
      "a": "drink no",
      "b": "drink not",
      "c": "don't drink",
      "d": "not drink",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ doing that, will you!",
      "a": "Stops",
      "b": "You stop",
      "c": "Stop",
      "d": "Stop you",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is it going to rain? 'I _____'",
      "a": "hope so",
      "b": "hope yes",
      "c": "hope that",
      "d": "hope if",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- I hope so: used to say that you hope something that has been mentioned happens or is true ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}